ojolink.net 2012-09-06

# 

Terms and Conditions / _Privacy Policy_

OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) is project where the main characteristic is the provision of connections to different contents, websites with a verification of the connection to download free of virus and spywares, fast, without intermediate pages direct to the downloads owner websites. Working like a download directory. 

OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) is in force by the international laws and is protected by intellectual and industrial property. Reserved rights.  
The Links provided in OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) are versions shareware, freeware or versions demo disclosed publicly by the authors of the same and is always realized from the Web site verified of author.  
Services  
\- File of contents ordered by categories.  
\- Revision of unloading availability and guarantee of the same every week.  
\- Service of analyses of virus known the links in the site  
\- Protection of the information of its clients.  
The user becomes person in charge of the damages that could be derived from the correct or incorrect use of links in this site.  
The services of OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) will visualize the information and contents, They could be could be downloading of software and content that is as long as they are subject to the laws of intellectual and industrial property and does not yield nor distributes the same without previous authorization of the author or creative company.  
This Web site does not become person in charge of the operation of the download programs, nor of possible problems collaterals that these programs could cause in their equipment  
This Web site does not become person in charge of the evil use that could realize the user of the download program or the infractions of the user or author that affects to the rights of author and intellectual property of other authors or third parties.  
In no case is allowed nor authorized in this Web site the publication of systems or means of infringement of the intellectual property (cracks, programs hackers or tools of violation of series.  
If at some time the user is not satisfied with the services offered in this website , will be able to asking for the information on the matter and an immediate access of the connection or downloading wished HERE.

The relation between the author and this Web site could at any time be terminated previous request of anyone of the two parts.  
Any manufacturer can ask for the actualization or request a retired of any of the applications link located in OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it )

 _PRIVACY POLICY_

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) uses and protects any information that you give OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) when you use this website.

OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st January 2008.

What we collect

We may collect the following information:

* name and job title

* contact information including email address

* demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests

* other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

* Internal record keeping.

* We may use the information to improve our products and services.

* We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.

* From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail.

* We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

* whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes

* if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it )

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to our postal address which you can obtain from the Contacts page.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.  
Thanks  
OJOLINK ( WEBSITES .com, .fr, .net, .it ) Team
